<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vufuzi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vufuzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 23:54:04 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 23:54:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The most efficient way to contact us if thorugh e-mail at &lt;a href=&#34;info@vufuzi.se&#34;&gt;info@vufuzi.se&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I you wanna call us, dial to &lt;a href=&#34;tel:0046725039148&#34;&gt;+46 72-503 91 48&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-media:3c4864f00d23f7ea35511ec930ce1d9c&#34;&gt;Social Media&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://facebook.com/Vufuzi&#34;&gt;Vufuzi on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Vufuzi&#34;&gt;Vufuzi on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://plus.google.com/+VufuziSe&#34;&gt;Vufuzi on Google Plus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 23:54:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pricing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-and-app-development:0120fabe74c55d02d54239cee6e78332&#34;&gt;Web and App Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We´re flexible in our pricing. For web development we charge 400 SEK (exclusive VAT) per hour. Fixed prices can be arranged as well, starting from 5 000 SEK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-hosting:0120fabe74c55d02d54239cee6e78332&#34;&gt;Website Hosting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our environmental friendly hosting solution is 100 SEK per month exclusive VAT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-maintenance:0120fabe74c55d02d54239cee6e78332&#34;&gt;Website Maintenance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping a website updated and compliant to the latest standars is important for both you and your users. We offer maintenance for 300 SEK / month, VAT excluded.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 23:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-development:bfc9941b6b6fd7b4ef09dd0ccd08af0c&#34;&gt;Web Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We craft simple, yet beautiful websites with modern techniques and the latest code standards. If you wish to have a CMS, Content Management System, that can be arranged. We always do Search Engine Optimization (SEO). baked into our products!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-hosting:bfc9941b6b6fd7b4ef09dd0ccd08af0c&#34;&gt;Web Hosting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy any of our services you will get the oppotunitto let us host your website with our environmental friendly web hosting. All energy used to power the servers are generated by wind energy. And, for each kWh used, twice as many RECs are bought to compensate up to 200 percent. This would be equal to planting 244 acres of trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;app-development:bfc9941b6b6fd7b4ef09dd0ccd08af0c&#34;&gt;App Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can also help you make apps for mobile phones and the web. We make these with web techonologies. We can make apps for Windows Phone, iOS, Android, Chrome Web Store, Mac, Windows and Linux.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vufuzi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 23:51:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We´re a creative company from western Värmland wich offers services in web development. We create, host and maintain your website, blog, app and e-commerce site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work with the latest technologies in web development and web design to deliver a good product that stands up over time. When you do business with us, you need not worry about anything regarding the website when we are finished making it. We make sure to keep your code up to date and modern so your site always remains fresh and continues to work for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By optimizing your website for search engines (SEO) we increase your chances to get closer, or at, the top of Google, Binf and Tahoo. This is a very important thing for a business which are to have customers online. You can think of it like the Yellow Pages of today. If your company is not in it, you will not get as many customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we create your website we will do it with responsive and adaptive web design to ensure that it can be used with ease one desktop computers, tablets and mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking to build a website that puts you, your company or your organization at the forefront now and in the future? Do you need a new web design for your current website? A whole new blog? Do not hesitate to contact us. We´ll do the best we can to help you out. Quickly, cheaply and professionally.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>